http://www.animaticmedia.com/privacypolicy

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.
Privacy Policy
Animatic Media Inc, “Animatic Media” “we,” “us,” “our”), is committed to letting you know how we will collect and use your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement is applicable to your use of the Animatic Media websites (the “Website”). We have established this Privacy Statement to let you know the kinds of information we may gather when you use the Website, why we gather your information, what we use your information for, when we might disclose your info rmation, and how you can manage your information.>
This Privacy Statement does not apply to information that users may submit to us offline, by email or other electronic file transmission not facilitated by our Website, or to third-party websites that may be linked to or from the Website. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third-party websites.By using the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Website. We reserve the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Statement from time to time. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes.
Information Collected
We collect personal data including personally identifiable information (PII) from you, for example, when you subscribe to our newsletter, when you apply to a job offer, complete a survey, or when you request information from us. By submitting such data, you explicitly consent to our data processing, for the purpose described.
The personal information we collect includes, for example, preferences, email addresses, click stream and navigation data.
Please be assured that all information we collect is collected for a specific purpose and is necessary for this purpose and will not be used subsequently for another purpose.
We comply with with the EU Regulation 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR), If you ever find that information about you is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, we want to correct it. In compliance with the applicable law, we also stay at your disposal in order to access, rectify or request deletion of any data you provided us, by contacting us at hello@animaticmedia.com
Use of Your Information
We use the information we learn about you to help us personalise and continually improve your experience using the Website. We may use your information to: (1) provide requested content; (2) personalise content on our Website; (3) send you communications about our services or special events; (4) communicate with you and respond to inquiries; (5) optimise or improve the Website and our operations; (6) detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal; and (7) perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Website.
We may also use or combine information that we collect through the Website with information that we collect about you offline to enhance, expand, and check the accuracy of our records.
Sharing Your Information
We may disclose your personal information collected via the Website to our agents, affiliates, partners, and other third parties, as described below. We may disclose information that does not specifically and personally identify you, such as aggregate information, device identifiers or other unique identifiers to third parties.
Third-Party Agents and Service Providers: We have third-party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and service providers that perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, hosting, providing the platform used to deliver the Website, technical integration, hosting, and analytics. These entities may have access to personal information, if needed, to perform their functions.
Assignment: We may change our ownership or corporate organisation while providing the Website. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Website. In such event, we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity acquiring all or part of our assets or to another entity with which we have merged.
Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations: We may also use or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or on the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:
(1) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website;
(2) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, or
(3) act to protect the personal safety of us, users of the Website, or the public.
Cookies & Tracking Technologies
The Website uses “cookies” to collect information about your visit and to manage your preferences. A cookie is a small computer code added to a file on your computer as a record of its visit. It does not collect or provide your personal information. It can, however, be used to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, to better tailor the Website for you. We may share information obtained from the varying kinds of cookies with third parties, including vendors, advertisers and others. You can control what cookies are accepted by your device through the settings on your browser or by deleting them. Doing so, however, may limit the personalisation available to you.
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. on our Website. These analytics services uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyse how users interact with and use the Website, compile reports on activity, and provide other analytical services and reports. The technologies used by these analytics services may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, any referring website, and other information. Our Website does not use these analytics services to gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies. To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google click here.
Please note that, although your device may include “Do Not Track” functionality, Animatic Media’ information collection and disclosure practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.
Opting-Out of Email Marketing Communications
You may always opt-out of receiving future email marketing messages from Animatic Media. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each marketing email. Please note that you may not opt-out of our service-related communications.
Children’s Privacy
This site is targeted at persons aged 16 and older. Animatic Media does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16. If we learn that we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 16, we will delete the data from our systems. As legal guardians,parents are recommended to supervise the online activity of their children and determine which sites are appropriate.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, you should contact us by email at hello@animaticmedia.com.
ABOUT
We’re Animatic Media- an elite team of animators, 3D artists, visual effect artists, editors videographers and storyboard artists that help our clients craft and refine stories for animatics, market research, social media and broadcast. We work fast and fun and bring over 28 years of experience to our projects offering exceptional quality and better outcomes for our clients.
ABOUT
BLOG
PRICING
JOBS
CONTACT
SERVICES
ANIMATICS
ANIMATION
©2002-2020 Animatic Media Inc. is a Veteran and MBE certified owned companyPrivacy Policy
